<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>All about Neil Alfred Salazar</title>
    <link>https://polite-dune-093dc2900.3.azurestaticapps.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on All about Neil Alfred Salazar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:04:06 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://polite-dune-093dc2900.3.azurestaticapps.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://polite-dune-093dc2900.3.azurestaticapps.net/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 21:04:06 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polite-dune-093dc2900.3.azurestaticapps.net/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>Myself
Myself
Myself
About Myself I currently reside in the charming town of Alfonso, located in the province of Cavite in the Philippines. Nestled amidst picturesque landscapes, Alfonso offers a tranquil and serene environment that I&amp;rsquo;m fortunate to call home. As for my educational journey, I have recently completed my college studies, marking a significant milestone in my life. The experiences and knowledge I gained during my time at Cavite State University Main Campus and took a bachelor degree in Information Technology have shaped me in profound ways, preparing me for the next chapter of my journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hobby</title>
      <link>https://polite-dune-093dc2900.3.azurestaticapps.net/posts/hobby/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 09:45:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polite-dune-093dc2900.3.azurestaticapps.net/posts/hobby/</guid>
      <description>I am engaging in a variety of hobbies brings me immense joy and fulfillment. I have a strong passion for music, particularly playing musical instruments like the trombone, sausaphone euphonium. The melodies that flow from these instruments allow me to express myself in ways words cannot. Additionally, I find solace in percussion instruments, where rhythm becomes my language. Beyond the realm of music, I find myself on the basketball court, where the thrill of the game and the camaraderie with teammates invigorate me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IT Related Projects</title>
      <link>https://polite-dune-093dc2900.3.azurestaticapps.net/posts/image/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 09:45:54 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://polite-dune-093dc2900.3.azurestaticapps.net/posts/image/</guid>
      <description>These are projects that I made during my college days and internship.
JoJe E-Commerce Website
Web-based Contact Tracing System
Simple Calculator
IT Related Projects JoJe E-commerce website - I am one of the member who build the project for JoJe Philippines. I am a back-end web developer for this project. Web-based Contact Tracing System - It is my Capstone Project in my college days and also, I am a back-end web developer for this project.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
